原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     VioletCheng  二糯米  屯栗子
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
扮巴仔超人
我们最爱的辛普森一家
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第四集
万圣节快乐
如果你看见骷髅  它绝不是装饰品
再来一个长的就成了
Come on. One more long one and we can get this thing done.
恭喜  是个男孩
Congratulations! It's a boy.
是个女孩
什么
What?
又是个男孩  除了巴仔之外
Another boy? Plus Bart?
急诊[勃起]
好像把弗兰肯斯坦介绍给德古拉
That's like introducing Frankenstein to Dracula.
或是把切尼介绍给布什
Or Cheney to Bush.
或是把本·阿弗莱克介绍给任何人
Or Ben Affleck to anybody.
虽然不太正规  但是
Hmm. Well, this is unorthodox, but, uh,
你愿不愿意用一个可爱的女宝宝取代
what would you think about taking a cute baby girl instead?
她妈妈难产死了
Her mother died in childbirth.
她爸爸是10000个疯子之一
The, uh, father is listed as 10,000 lunatics,
但是他们中任何人都没露过面
but, uh, none of them has shown up yet.
缺货
-成交  -不过我得告诉你
- Sold. - I should warn you, however.
我们在她身上做了例行检查
We ran the standard newborn screen on her,
检测出她具有邪恶
and, uh, she tested positive
阳性
for evil.
还是比个男孩好多了
Still better than a boy.
阿麦小可爱
Maggie darling,
这么多小动物都是你毛茸茸的新伙伴
these stuffed animals are your fuzzy new friends.
这是宝宝的第一个音乐盒
And here's baby's first music box.
牛说...
The cow says...
你老妈在地狱里跟运动员约会
your mother dates jocks in hell.
尼莫跟你一样
Aw, Nemo's just like you.
他的妈妈也难产死了
His mommy died at the beginning, too.
是的没错
Yes, she did.
预兆
"预兆"
"Omen"!
赛车总动员
[英文正反是一样的]
预兆
是回文
Palindrome!
又回来了
Callback!
我开始怀疑用这个不明出生的孩子
I'm beginning to wonder if trading for this baby
当替代品是不是一件正确的事情
of unknown origin was the right thing to do.
马姬  我喂过宝宝啦
Marge, I fed the baby!
阿麦生日快乐
宝宝叫我们自杀
The baby is making us kill ourselves.
我以为只有我们俩自杀
I thought this suicide was just gonna be the two of us.
咱们到地狱里弄明白吧
We'll figure it out in hell!
我必须阻止这个撒旦之子
Oh, I must stop this spawn of Satan.
但我真的可以杀害一个小宝宝吗
But can I really find it in my heart to kill a child?
我喜欢莫里西
I like Morrissey.
生活不如意啊[《四个毕业生》]
Reality bites.
看来我得准备三个坟墓
Looks like I'll be digging three graves.
内德  住手
Ned, stop!
它必须被杀死  它有野兽之印
It must be killed. It bears the mark of the beast.
抱歉  不是这个
Sorry, not that one.
《假如腹中孩子是反基督者该怎么办》
我们该怎么办  怎么办
What do we do? What do we do?
还是比男孩好
Still better than a boy.
万圣节特辑
恐怖树屋
第666集
或者第667集
如果福克斯台改了时间的话
危险物语
八十年代
他们永远不会改进这个游戏
They'll never improve on this game.
我妈妈不让我看电影
My mom won't let me see the movie
因为她觉得科学家会吓到我
'cause she thinks the scientists will scare me.
我们得走了
We'd better go.
降落裤  激活
Parachute pants, activate.
晚点见
Smell ya later.
*我独自骑车车*
*Riding all alone*
*我会安全回到...*
*I shall get back safely...*
靠  我从来没唱完过安全歌
Dang. I never get to finish my "Safely" Song.
露安  我的名片夹名片不够了
Luann! I need extra cards for my Rolodex!
作为一个雅皮士  我要交到更多朋友才行
As a yuppie, I'm making lots more friends.
苗浩斯还没到家
Milhouse still isn't home.
现在还是凌晨两点
And it's 2:00 in the morning.
我的斯沃琪手表显示七点半
My Swatch watch says 7:30.
看  分针刚过唇印
Uh, see? Squiggle hand is just past the kissy lips.
等一下  那是时针
Wait, no, that's the zigzag hand.
时  时针
The zig-- the zigzag hand?!
苗浩斯  你在哪里
Milhouse, where are you?
拜托
Oh, come on.
也许他在这面墙里
Maybe he's in this wall.
柯克  你疯了
Kirk, you're going crazy.
疯了  我疯了吗
Crazy?! Am I?!
在你看来这块表也疯了吗  露安
Does this look crazy to you, Luann?
这也疯了吗
Does this?
你朋友的车子丢在这了
Your friend's bike crashed here.
我们在这找到了他的吸入器
We found his inhaler here.
这里是他最后留下的尿渍
And over here is his final pee stain.
他昨晚的确喝了很多新可乐[1985年]
He did drink a lot of New Cokes last night.
现在到底是什么年代了
Look, what the hell year is this anyway?
我真的是迷糊了
I'm really getting confused.
如果苗浩斯真的进入了另一个维度
If Milhouse is in another dimension,
他可以通过让这些小灯闪烁来跟我们沟通
he can communicate with us by blinking these lights.
来吧  苗浩斯  你可以的
Come on, Milhouse. You can do it.
承认吧  我们的儿子不在了
Admit it. Our son is gone.
所以  我可以告诉你
So, I can tell you.
我有外遇了
I've been having an affair.
是苗浩斯的霹雳舞老师吗
Is it Milhouse's break dancing tutor?
你告诉他了吗
Did you tell him yet?
先别急
Uh... Hold your horses.
SOS[救命]
现在不行  苗浩斯
Not now, Milhouse!
爸爸妈妈在大声讲话呢
Mommy and Daddy are loud talking!
不如你先回自己的房间去吧  宝贝
Why don't you go to your room, sweetie?
喂喂喂  省着点用电  儿子
Whoa, whoa. Easy on the electric bill there, son.
你好  你好
Hello? Hello?
丽莎在吗
Uh, I-is Lisa there?
苗浩斯
Milhouse?
这要看情况
Uh, that depends.
你喜欢苗浩斯吗
Do you like Milhouse?
我喜欢苗浩斯  但是不是那种喜欢
I like Milhouse, but I don't like like Milhouse.
打错了
Wrong number!
老鼠法庭购物中心
苗浩斯还活着  我刚刚和他说完话
Milhouse is alive. I just talked to him!
我觉得他在另一个维度里
I think he's in another dimension.
我是我玩的最好的一局  不玩完绝对不走
This is my best game ever. I'm not leaving till it's done.
快点  巴仔
Come on, Bart!
成吧
Fine.
你们可以通过这个感官剥夺箱
You can reach the parallel dimension
到达与我们平行的维度
via this sensory deprivation tank.
需要一个有异常强大心智的人
It requires somebody with an extraordinary power of mind.
格莱文
Glavin.
你为什么剃了个秃头
Why did you shave your head?
是为了增强导电性吗
Was it to increase conductivity?
不  我就是想剪个刘海
No, I was trying to give myself bangs
然后它们就都离我而去了
and it got away from me.
现在咱们开始吧
Now let's do this thing.
我做到了
I made it.
我到了下面的世界
I'm in the Over Under.
苗浩斯
Milhouse!
你随时都可以逃跑的
You could've escaped anytime!
被环抱的感觉很爽
It felt nice to be embraced.
好了  秘密就是
Okay, here's the secret.
一动不动他们就看不到你了
Just hold still and they can't see you.
看见了吧
See?
我们完美地  完美地
We are perfectly, perfectly...
我忘了我们也不该讲话的
I forgot we're not supposed to talk either.
不走运啊  老兄
Tough luck, dude.
我的天
Oh, my God!
这里是被扭曲过的现实
It's a twisted version of reality.
甜甜圈
安卓地下城勇士与棒球卡片商店
老谋子酒馆
看起来有些人没怎么看过第三季
It seems like someone hasn't seen very much of season three.
你们好吗  替我向你妈妈问好
How ya doin'? Say hi to your mom.
我最好用我的通灵能力
I'd better use my psychic powers.
我不知道你还能通灵
I didn't know you had psychic powers.
女孩们不敢用
Girls are afraid to use them,
因为那时候我们不能被称为女性
because then we're called unfeminine.
我们在塞勒姆不必要地失去了很多优秀的女巫
We needlessly lost a lot of good witches at Salem.
塞勒姆1962年的一场女巫审判
当地共1500人  150人被当做是女巫吊死
现在我有能力不去健身了
Now I have the power to skip gym!
-爸爸  -安静  宝贝
- Dad? - Quiet, sweetie.
爸爸在工作呢
Daddy's at work.
伯恩斯先生打开了通往另一维度的通道
Mr. Burns opened a portal to another dimension
放出了好多怪兽
that released a lot of monsters.
他在找什么
What was he looking for?
这都是一个政府秘密计划的一部分
It's all part of a secret government program
找到怪兽
to find monsters.
这只怪兽吃了卡尔  但是因为卡尔在他体内
A monster ate Carl, but because Carl's inside him,
这只怪兽就是我的朋友了
the monster's my friend.
他还记得我们儿时的事情
He remembers when we were kids
我们会一起去
and we used to go down to...
好了  他们不会再烦我们了
Well, they won't bother us anymore.
你们安全了
You kids are safe.
只是我们被永远困在这个维度里了
But we are trapped in this dimension forever.
谁想坐在我的肩上走一程
Who wants a piggyback ride?
永远困住
Trapped forever?
这里也不算太差
It's not so bad here.
天哪  这些藤蔓总能找到所有小洞
Boy, these vines sure are good at finding all the holes.
在下面的世界  能买得起房子
In the Over Under, housing is affordable,
学校都很棒
schools are excellent,
你还能步行到商店和餐厅
and you can walk to shops and restaurants.
亚马逊送货到这里吗
Does Amazon deliver here?
他们有一支飞行怪兽送货小队
They have a fleet of flying monsters.
这里至少有一点好
Well, there is one thing that's better.
至少没有愚蠢的
At least there's no stupid...
你好呀  亲爱的邻居
Howdily-doodily, neighborino!
天堂  向右滑
春田原子体育场
春田原子队  对战  谢尔比维尔队
先生们  现在是最后一次带球触地进攻了
Well, sir, it's fourth down and goal to go.
四分卫凯斯·迪格斯拿到了球
Quarterback Case Diggs takes the ball.
滴答滴答滴答  最后三秒钟
Hickory dickory dock, three ticks left on the clock.
他在看时机  他掷球了
He looks. He throws.
球被截住了
Intercepted!
四分卫发挥失常了
The quarterback choked.
烂球  烂球  烂球
Choke, choke, choke!
有热狗
Hot dog!
烂球[也有噎住的意思]
Choke!
烂球  烂球  烂球
Choke, choke, choke,
烂球  烂球
choke, choke...!
烂球  烂球  烂球
Choke, choke, choke!
天堂
侯默·辛普森  欢迎来到天堂
Homer Simpson, welcome to Heaven.
你就是圣彼得吗
Are you Saint Peter?
不  我是圣格雷特尔  请原谅这里的双关
No, I'm Saint Greeter, if you'll forgive the pun.
greeter有迎宾员的意思
我才不原谅
I don't forgive it.
你这该死的
Damn you...!
天堂和我想的不一样
Hmm. Heaven doesn't look like I expected.
没错  因为上帝投靠了谷歌
Yeah. God sold out to Google.
我真不知道我做得对不对
I really wonder if I did the right thing.
迈阿密马林鱼队
飓风警报
看来全球变暖是真的
Maybe global warming is real.
接下来播出
四点十五  来自炼狱
天堂
天哪  大事不妙
Oh, my. This is not good.
这可不好  根据这上面说的
Not good! Okay, according to this,
你还不该到这里来
you're not supposed to be here yet.
我们得送你回去
We have to send you back.
我又能见到马姬了吗
I get to see Marge again?
还可以吃掉我放在冰箱里的那盒千层面吗
And eat that tub of lasagna I have in the refrigerator?
它最好还在那
It better still be there.
快把我送回去
Send me back now!
听着  我很乐意  好吗
Look, I would love to, okay?
但是当时医护人员抬不动你的尸体
But the paramedics couldn't lift your corpse,
所以他们就把你滚进了湖里
so they rolled it into a lake.
浮肿得厉害
Pretty bloated.
等等  这是扔进去之前的照片
Ah. Wait. That's the before picture.
这是之后的照片
Here's the after picture.
这是很久之后的照片
And here's the way after picture.
这太恶心了
It's, uh, pretty disgusting.
你得把我送回到马姬身边
You've got to get me back to Marge.
好了  知道了
Yeah, okay, got it, got it.
我们打乱一下规矩
We'll disrupt the paradigm.
侯默  我们可以把你放进一个
Homer, we're gonna put you in the body of someone
今天本会死的人的身体里  你就用他们活吧
who's supposed to die today, and you can live as them.
我能住在猪的身体里吗
Ooh. Can I live in the body of a pig?
我喜欢不用穿裤子的自由感
I like the freedom of not wearing pants.
想要变成猪  有一个六个月长的等候名单
Oh, there's a six-month waiting list to be a pig.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
就这样吗
E-be-de-be-de-be-de. That's all?
就从这些里面选一个吧  好吗
Look, just choose one of these, okay?
不行
Hmm. No.
不
No.
挺吸引人  但不
Tempting, but no.
不
No.
不可能
Forget it.
就他了
That's the one!
伙计  我在这等好久了
Hey, man, I've been waiting here a long time.
秃顶时代
年度男性
有什么事吗
Hello?
好久不见  马姬
Hello, Marge.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
别怕  是我  你丈夫侯默
Now, don't freak out, but it's me, your husband Homer.
我死了  现在在这个足球运动员的身体里
I died, and I'm inside the body of this football player.
你看我相信吗
How could I possibly believe that?
我知道你不为人知的小秘密
Because I know something about you that no one else knows.
-什么秘密  -忘了
- What's that? - I forget.
真的是你
It's you!
赘肉  肌肉
Fat, fit.
肥胖  健美
Portly, sportly.
果冻  瞧瞧这肉体
Jell-O? Hello!
不管是谁的肉体  我爱的是里面的男人
Mm, whatever body you're in, I love the guy inside.
老天保佑  我摸到了腹肌
Oh, my God, I touched an ab.
我还以为腹肌都是假的
I didn't think abs were real.
和其他已婚男人的肉体亲热
It's really weird snuggling with the body of a man
感觉好奇怪
who's married to someone else.
这可不是一般肉体  是德州裸体小姐
Not just someone, Miss Nude Texas.
好吧马姬  我去找个别人的身体
All right, Marge. I'll find someone else's body.
等等等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
老侯  老侯
Homie? Homie?
你一夜之间就毁了这身材
You ruined that body in one night?
葬礼剩下的食物真的很好吃
The funeral leftovers were so good.
太可怕了  我要换人
This is too creepy. I want something else.
死掉的年轻人越来越少了  真悲剧
It's a real tragedy more young people don't die.
爹  你能当校监查尔默斯
Dad! You could be Superintendent Chalmers,
他是我们校长的老板
my principal's boss.
马姬  你觉得呢
Marge, what do you say?
我挺希望他能有个伴
I would like to see Chalmers with somebody.
他太孤独了
He's so lonely.
好  他死了
Boom. He's dead.
你 你叫我吗  老板
You-you wanted to see me, sir?
史金纳
Skinner!
由于新的学校规定
Because of new school rules,
从此以后  巴仔的每门课都必须得优秀
from now on, Bart gets all A's.
把你的乳头扭成紫色
Give yourself a purple nurple.
再扭  继续扭
Purpler. Purpler.
已经是纯靛蓝色了
This is pure indigo.
他说了继续
He said, "Purpler."
好的老板
Yes, sir.
敬新生活
A toast to my new life
从此我就是公立学校主管了
as public school administrator.
现在看看我的工资有多少
And now to open my paycheck and see what I make.
下一个
Next.
这太疯狂了
This has gotten out of hand.
你换身体太频繁了
You're changing bodies so much,
我已经不知道我嫁给谁了
I don't even know who I'm married to anymore.
难怪我在《人猿星球》里
Oh, so that's why
站在猩猩一边
I'm rooting for the apes in Planet of the Apes.
拜托你  选定一个合适的
Oh, please, just pick one man
然后我们一起继续好好生活
I can be with for the rest of my life.
他不必完美
He doesn't have to be perfect.
只要像你一样爱我就好
He just has to love me like you do.
我知道是谁了
Hmm. I know just the guy.
我一开始有些担心  但看来这能行
Well, I had my doubts, but this works.
我觉得很好  我的脑子和老谋子的身体
This is great. My brain in Moe's body.
而我的脑子在这呢
Yeah, and I'm in here.
米姬
And, uh, Midge, I'm, uh...
我渴了
I'm very thirsty.
多毛女遇上粘液怪
我是史上第一个被车管局
So, I'm the first person to ever be fired
以态度恶劣为由被炒的人
by the DMV for a bad attitude.
也算厉害了
Isn't that something?
算吗
Huh? Isn't it?
我不哑  只是不想和你说话
最高戒备
未经授权  不得进入
我得去抽根烟
I need to sneak a smoke.
我是征服者康康
I am Kang the Conqueror.
我是空闲者塞尔玛
I am Selma the available.
太浪漫了
This is so romantic.
让我好好看看你
Let me get a look at you.
你不喜欢你所见到的
Oh, you don't like what you see.
正相反
Quite the contrary.
"啊哈"就是我们形容"美丽"的词
"Aah" is our word for "Beautiful."
变态
Freak.
你能转过来吗
Can you turn yourself?
我们要亲热了
We're gonna make out.
赶紧杀了我吧
Just kill me now.
怎么了  亲爱的
What's wrong, my darling?
你姐姐说你只是想吃掉我  或者为了拿绿卡
My sister says you just want to eat me, or for a green card.
或者是人类动物园
Or a human zoo.
有两个太荒谬了
Two of those are ridiculous.
快点  躲起来
Quick! Hide!
你好  只是想让你知道
Hello. Just want you to know
我们明天会解剖你
we'll be dissecting you tomorrow.
但是我可以告诉你干净天然能源的秘密
But I could teach you the secret of clean, natural energy.
那我今晚就解剖你
Then I'll dissect you tonight.
我们得把你救出来
We have to save you!
你想干什么
What do you want?
你愿意我去一个遥远星系永远不回来吗
How'd you like me to go to a distant galaxy and never return?
你打电话了吗
You rang?
我们来救你出去的  亲爱的
We've come to get you out, my love.
哎呦  已经要用"爱"这个字眼了是吧
Oh, we're using the "L" Word, huh?
应该好好谈谈的  不过没关系
Should've been a conversation, but okay.
这东西里面都是老鼠
This thing is full of rats.
真体贴
Very thoughtful.
别动  辛普森  你想干什么
Hold it right there, Simpson. What are you up to?
我这个...你知道
Um, I am, uh, you know,
编个故事  拖拖时间
uh, cover story, stalling for time,
编故事  吞吞吐吐  支支吾吾
cover story, hemming, hawing,
借口  不在场证明
excuse, alibi.
促销
Promotion?
别往车上开枪  你得瞄准司机
Don't shoot at the van. Shoot at the driver.
别瞄我的司机
Not my driver.
我的伙伴蝌蚪会在春田山顶与我们汇合
My partner Kodos will meet us at the top of Mount Springfield.
-伙伴  -写作伙伴
- Partner? - Writing partner.
他们跟我们说  如果你们想进军演艺界
They told us, if you want to make it in showbiz,
你得来地球[脚踏实地]
You have to be on earth.
春田镇
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我搞错了  我去的是南方赢了内战的那个地球
By mistake. I went to that other earth where the South won the Civil War.
同盟军纪念碑少得多的多
Far fewer Confederate monuments.
我被击中了
I've been hit.
稍等  我亲爱的
One moment, my love.
啊哈哈哈  我没事
Nah! Nah! Miss me.
别害怕  我淫荡的小烟囱
Fear not, my sultry smokestack.
我能治好你
I can heal you.
亲爱的  或许你该少抽点
Maybe you should cut down a little, dear.
为了我们的孩子
For the baby.
你是说
You mean... ?
没错  我怀孕了
That's right. I'm pregnant. Mmm.
塞尔玛  不要
Selma, no!
你们太不同了
You two are too different.
你是狮子座  他是射手座
You're a Leo, and he's a Sagittarius.
我来自射手座
I'm from Sagittarius.
别走  塞尔玛  求你
Oh, don't go, Selma. Please.
没有你我活不下去
I can't live without you.
我得警告你
I have to warn you...
我是同性恋
I'm gay.
那好说  我有32种性别身份
That's all right. I have 32 sexual identities.
我上能睡克林贡人
I'm Klingon curious,
下对伍基人来者不拒
always up for some Wookiee nookie
左可以跟R2机器人3P
or an R2 threesome,
右可以驾驭深空九号生物
not to mention some Deep Space Nine,
就是赫特人贾霸也能睡到飞起
or possibly Jabba the Butt.
你喜欢蜜月星球吗
Are you enjoying the honeymoon planet?
为什么不在凉快的季节来呢
Why didn't we come here in the cool season?
已经是凉快的季节了
This is the cool season.
亲爱的要毛衣吗
Shall I get a sweater for you, dear?
这里特么4000度
It's 4,000 degrees.
你真是唠叨
Nag, nag, nag.
万圣节特辑
恐怖树屋
第666集纪念